var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "But came to them",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "fa-atāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاكُمُ",
        "answer": "gives you",
        "pcklId": "514",
        "tlit": "ātākumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "they were given",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْثِرُونَ",
        "answer": "but prefer",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wayu'thirūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُذُوهُ",
        "answer": "take it",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "fakhudhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِإِخْوَانِنَا",
        "answer": "and our brothers",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wali-ikh'wāninā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِإِخْوَانِهِمُ",
        "answer": "to their brothers",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "li-ikh'wānihimu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "it (was) by the permission",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fabi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُصُولِهَا",
        "answer": "their roots",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "uṣūlihā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "530",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "638",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "639",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1313",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1314",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1315",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1316",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1317",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "1318",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "towards those who",
        "pcklId": "1319",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1320",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1321",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those",
        "pcklId": "1322",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "you (who)",
        "pcklId": "1323",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "like those who",
        "pcklId": "1324",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1325",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1326",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "[to] Allah",
        "pcklId": "2637",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2638",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2639",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2640",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2641",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2642",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2643",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2644",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2645",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2646",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2647",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2648",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(it is) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2649",
        "tlit": "falillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2650",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2651",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2652",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2653",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2654",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2655",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2656",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2657",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2658",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2659",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2660",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2661",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2662",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2663",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2664",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2665",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "673",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "674",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their affair",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "amrihim",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِيمَانَ",
        "answer": "and (accepted) faith",
        "pcklId": "645",
        "tlit": "wal-īmāna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِيمَانِ",
        "answer": "in faith",
        "pcklId": "646",
        "tlit": "bil-īmāni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the believers",
        "pcklId": "832",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "the Giver of Security",
        "pcklId": "850",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْإِنْسَانِ",
        "answer": "to man",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "lil'insāni",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "the People",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَوَّلِ",
        "answer": "at (the) first",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "li-awwali",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أُولِي",
        "answer": "O those endowed",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "yāulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their violence",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "basuhum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرِيءٌ",
        "answer": "disassociated",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "barīon",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَارِئُ",
        "answer": "the Inventor",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-bāri-u",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْصَارِ",
        "answer": "(with) insight",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-abṣāri",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْتَغُونَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yabtaghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنِ",
        "answer": "and",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَوَّءُوا",
        "answer": "settled",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "tabawwaū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُيُوتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their houses",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "buyūtahum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among themselves",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَكْتُمُوهَا",
        "answer": "you left them",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "taraktumūhā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَبَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Irresistible",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-jabāru",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَبَلٍ",
        "answer": "a mountain",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "jabalin",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُدُرٍ",
        "answer": "walls",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "judurin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) recompense",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "put",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "tajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَلَاءَ",
        "answer": "the exile",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-jalāa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "(are) united",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوا",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "jāū",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّونَ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbūna",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْسَبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "You think they",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "taḥsabuhum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْتَسِبُوا",
        "answer": "they expected",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yaḥtasibū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the beautiful",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَشْرِ",
        "answer": "gathering",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ḥashri",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُصُونُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their fortresses",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥuṣūnuhum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحَصَّنَةٍ",
        "answer": "fortified",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "muḥaṣṣanatin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاجَةً",
        "answer": "any want",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥājatan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِبُونَ",
        "answer": "they destroyed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yukh'ribūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُوا",
        "answer": "they would leave",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yakhrujū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَخْرُجَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely we will leave",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "lanakhrujanna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُونَ",
        "answer": "they will leave",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yakhrujūna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "expelled",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرِجُوا",
        "answer": "were expelled",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ukh'rijū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرِجْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are expelled",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "ukh'rij'tum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرِجُوا",
        "answer": "they are expelled",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ukh'rijū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُخْزِيَ",
        "answer": "and that He may disgrace",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waliyukh'ziya",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعًا",
        "answer": "humbled",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "khāshiʿan",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشْيَةِ",
        "answer": "(the) fear",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "khashyati",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَصَاصَةٌ",
        "answer": "poverty",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khaṣāṣatun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "abiding forever",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "khālidayni",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِقُ",
        "answer": "the Creator",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "l-khāliqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "I fear",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْلٍ",
        "answer": "horses",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khaylin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَدْبَارَ",
        "answer": "(their) backs",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-adbāra",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their homes",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "diyārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِيَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their homes",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "diyārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارَ",
        "answer": "(in) the home",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-dāra",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُولَةً",
        "answer": "a (perpetual) circulation",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dūlatan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَاقُوا",
        "answer": "they tasted",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "dhāqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(are) Full of Kindness",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "raūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَأَيْتَهُ",
        "answer": "surely you (would) have seen it",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "lara-aytahu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "864",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "865",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "866",
        "tlit": "rabba",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلَهُ",
        "answer": "(to) His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "rusulahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "440",
        "tlit": "walilrrasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانًا",
        "answer": "and pleasure",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّعْبَ",
        "answer": "[the] terror",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ruʿ'ba",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِكَابٍ",
        "answer": "camels",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "rikābin",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَهْبَةً",
        "answer": "(in) fear",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "rahbatan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَّحَ",
        "answer": "Glorifies",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "sabbaḥa",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُ",
        "answer": "Glorifies",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory (be to)",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقُونَا",
        "answer": "preceded us",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "sabaqūnā",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "the wayfarer",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسَاكِينِ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wal-masākīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَلِّطُ",
        "answer": "gives power",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yusalliṭu",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّلَامُ",
        "answer": "the Giver of Peace",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-salāmu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) the names",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-asmāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "equal",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَتَّىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) divided",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shattā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُحَّ",
        "answer": "(from) stinginess",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shuḥḥa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(are) more intense",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاقُّوا",
        "answer": "they opposed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "shāqqū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشَاقِّ",
        "answer": "opposes",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yushāqqi",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُ",
        "answer": "bears witness",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yashhadu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "and the witnessed",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "wal-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "and (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(The) companions",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their breasts",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ṣudūrihim",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their breasts",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ṣudūrihim",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَصَدِّعًا",
        "answer": "breaking asunder",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mutaṣaddiʿan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the truthful",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqūna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصَوِّرُ",
        "answer": "the Fashioner",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-muṣawiru",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَضْرِبُهَا",
        "answer": "We present them",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "naḍribuhā",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُطِيعُ",
        "answer": "we will obey",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "nuṭīʿu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you think",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "and they thought",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْتَبِرُوا",
        "answer": "So take a lesson",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'tabirū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَذَّبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "certainly He (would) have punished them",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "laʿadhabahum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابُ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَتَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(the) end of both of them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatahumā",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) penalty",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) penalty",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they reason",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "543",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمُ",
        "answer": "(the) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "838",
        "tlit": "ʿālimu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِغَدٍ",
        "answer": "for tomorrow",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "lighadin",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "forgive",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "igh'fir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "غِلًّا",
        "answer": "any rancor",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ghillan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَغْنِيَاءِ",
        "answer": "the rich",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-aghniyāi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلًا",
        "answer": "bounty",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "faḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْفُقَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "For the poor",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "lil'fuqarāi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "give thought",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَائِزُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the achievers",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-fāizūna",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَاءَ",
        "answer": "(was) restored",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "afāa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَاءَ",
        "answer": "(was) restored",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "afāa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوتِلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are fought",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "qūtil'tum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوتِلُوا",
        "answer": "they are fought",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "qūtilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "will they fight you",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūnakum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُدُّوسُ",
        "answer": "the Holy One",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-qudūsu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَتْ",
        "answer": "it has sent forth",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "qaddamat",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَذَفَ",
        "answer": "and He cast",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waqadhafa",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "Quran",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the kindred",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبًا",
        "answer": "shortly",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qarīban",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the towns",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرًى",
        "answer": "towns",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "quran",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَطَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you cut down",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "qaṭaʿtum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "qulūbihimu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِنَا",
        "answer": "our hearts",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "qulūbinā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "but their hearts",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "waqulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "1530",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "saying",
        "pcklId": "1531",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he says",
        "pcklId": "1532",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he says",
        "pcklId": "1533",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "471",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "472",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَائِمَةً",
        "answer": "standing",
        "pcklId": "603",
        "tlit": "qāimatan",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَكَبِّرُ",
        "answer": "the Supreme",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "l-mutakabiru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "(had) decreed",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely liars",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "Disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "uk'fur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "he disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "it becomes",
        "pcklId": "1266",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1267",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانَ",
        "answer": "So will be",
        "pcklId": "1268",
        "tlit": "fakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "1269",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِينَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) palm-trees",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "līnatin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "Like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "Like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْثَالُ",
        "answer": "examples",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-amthālu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلِكُ",
        "answer": "the Sovereign",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-maliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَانِعَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "would defend them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "māniʿatuhum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their properties",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wa-amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (had) sent down",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "forgot",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْسَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "so He made them forget",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "fa-ansāhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْصُرُونَ",
        "answer": "and helping",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wayanṣurūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَنْصُرَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "certainly we will help you",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "lananṣurannakum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "they will help them",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yanṣurūnahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَرُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "they help them",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "naṣarūhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be helped",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْتَنْظُرْ",
        "answer": "and let look",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "waltanẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his soul",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "every soul",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَافَقُوا",
        "answer": "(were) hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nāfaqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَهَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "he forbids you",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "nahākum",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْتَهُوا",
        "answer": "refrain",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "fa-intahū",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to the people",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَاجَرَ",
        "answer": "emigrated",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "hājara",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهَاجِرِينَ",
        "answer": "emigrants",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-muhājirīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهَيْمِنُ",
        "answer": "the Guardian",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-muhayminu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَالَ",
        "answer": "(the) evil result",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wabāla",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "they find",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "yajidūna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْجَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you made expedition",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "awjaftum",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "warāi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوقَ",
        "answer": "is saved",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yūqa",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُوَلُّنَّ",
        "answer": "certainly they will turn",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "layuwallunna",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَتَامَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the orphans",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-yatāmā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their hands",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيْدِي",
        "answer": "and the hands",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "wa-aydī",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "59",
        "ayah": "2"
    }
]; 
export default words;